[ Cheers ]
[ 欢呼 ]
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Hi, everyone.
&gt;&gt;  大家好
Good morning.
早上好
Welcome to our session,
欢迎参加我们的大会
Introducing Business Chat
关于 Business Chat
Developer Preview.
开发者预览版的介绍
My name is Grant.
我是 Grant
And today, I'm going to give you
今天我将向大家
an overview of what Business
大致介绍下
Chat is and some of the new
什么是 Business Chat
features.
以及一些新功能
We'll also cover today what you
我们今天还会介绍在开发者预览版中
can do during the developer
你能做些什么
preview to get ready before the
以便在明年正式发布前
public launch next year.
做好准备
Later, my friend, Scotty, is
稍后  我的朋友 Scotty
going to come up and he's going
将会上台
to give us a demo of something
他将给大家带来
we're calling Business Chat
Business Chat Sandbox
Sandbox.
的演示
It's a great tool that going to
这是一个非常棒的工具
help you develop and test all
它能帮你开发以及测试
your solutions so that you're
你的方案
ready for the public launch.
以便你为公开发布做好准备
Are you ready?
你们准备好了吗？
Let's begin.
让我们开始吧
So the telephone has served us
对于消费者来说
well as customers but it's not
电话提供了很好的服务
always the most ideal way to
但对于企业来说
communicate with businesses.
却并非一直是最好的方式
Business Chat is important
Business Chat 很重要
because it offers a more
因为它提供了
flexible and more capable
更灵活以及
experience.
更强大的体验
For example, sometimes you're
比如有时你很忙
busy, you're running around.
手忙脚乱
You need a way to resolve issues
你需要一种
without dedicating your time to
不需要花时间打电话的方式
a phone call.
来解决问题
And you definitely don't want to
并且你绝对不想
waste your time waiting on hold.
浪费时间在等待接通上
You need a way to communicate in
你需要一种方式
between the million other things
能让你在所做的诸多事情之间
that you're doing, a way to
进行沟通交流
communicate on your schedule.
能让你根据日程表进行沟通交流
And a telephone call is not
打电话不具有视觉性
visual and it's definitely not
而且显然它没有
as capable as an iPhone.
iPhone 强大
Sometimes you need to show the
有时你需要向企业
business what you're seeing.
展示你所看到的
You might have an unfamiliar
你或许对某个产品不熟悉
product or need help with it or
或者需要帮助
maybe while you're chatting, you
或者当你在说话时
might need to do something
你可能需要进行一些互动
interactive like choosing from
比如从不同的选项中进行选择
different options, scheduling an
进行预约
appointment, making a payment,
进行支付
or even interacting with an app
或甚至和 App 进行互动
and that's Business Chat.
而这就是 Business Chat
It's a powerful way for
对于消费者来说
customers to communicate with
这是一个强大的沟通方式
you and to complete tasks.
能帮助我们更好的完成任务
Let's watch it in action.
让我们来看看演示
&gt;&gt; [Background Music]
&gt;&gt;  [背景音乐]
Introducing Business Chat, a
Business Chat
better way to make meaningful
是一种能让你和顾客
connections with your customers.
更好地建立良好关系的方式
With Business Chat, it's easy
有了 Business Chat
for customers to get in touch
当顾客需要你时
when they need you and you can
他们能很容易地与你取得联系
help them with everything, all
而你只需在一场消息对话中
in one message conversation,
便能为他提供各种帮助
have real interactions with your
当你回答他们的问题时
customers while answering their
就能进行
questions.
真实的互动
Help them learn more about your
帮助他们了解更多
products and link them straight
关于你产品的信息
to the information they're
以及将他们链接至
looking for.
他们需要的信息
Your customers can always come
你的顾客总是能
right back to chat again and
在此返回到对话中
with long-lived sessions, you'll
有了长期保留的对话
be ready with their information,
你会准备好他们的信息
so it's easy for them and easy
所以这对于你和他们
for you.
都很便捷
If customers already have a
如果顾客已经有
product in mind, they can make
想购买的产品
their purchase right in the
他们可以直接在消息对话中
message conversation with Apple
进行购买
Pay.
并用 Apple Pay 支付
Integration with Apple Pay means
Apple Pay 的接入意味着
customers can pay securely with
顾客可以安全支付
just one touch.
只需轻轻一点
They can also come back later to
他们还可以随后返回
track their orders.
来追踪自己的订单
All of this in one place.
所有的这些都在一处进行
With Business Chat, your
有了 Business Chat
customers can easily find you.
您的顾客可以轻易找到您
From Safari, Spotlight, Siri, or
从 Safari  Spotlight  Siri 或 Maps 上面
Maps, you're just a touch away.
只需轻轻一触
So everyone can enjoy faster,
每个人都能随时享受
seamless, more personal
快捷  无缝以及更加个性化的
interactions every time.
交流
Visit us to learn more.
请访问我们以了解更多
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; So today, we're opening up
&gt;&gt;  所以今天我们将向大家介绍
Business Chat as a Developer
Business Chat
Preview.
的开发者预览版
Business Chat is not launching
Business Chat 目前还不会
publicly yet because we want to
面向公众开放
make sure that we get this
因为我们想
right.
确保一切无误
We know that elevating the
我们知道要提升
customer service experience
顾客体验
takes coordination.
需要各方协调
It's going to take some time.
这需要一些时间
And we wanted to give you an
而且我们想要给你们机会
opportunity to get connected and
在正式公开发布之前去连接至 Business Chat
to integrate Business Chat into
并将
your operations ahead of the
它融入你们的
public launch.
运营当中
During the Developer Preview,
在预览版期间
Business Chat will be
Business Chat
operational but your business
是可以使用的的  但是你的企业
will not yet be publicly
无法被公开
accessible.
找到
You will, however, be able to
你可以将
white list some of your
你的一些员工列入白名单
employees who will be able to
他们可以
test your end-to-end experience
测试端对端的体验
to make sure that you're ready.
确保你已经做好准备
So let's talk about how we're
所以我们来谈一谈
making it easy for your
我们如何使顾客
customers to find you and to
轻易地找到你
start a conversation with your
并与你的企业
business.
进行对话
Once you have your Business Chat
一旦你有了 Business Chat 账户
account, message buttons will
Message 按钮将会
start appearing throughout iOS.
开始贯穿出现在 iOS 中
For example, this is how it
例如这就是在
would look in Safari.
Safari 中的样子
Customer might type your website
顾客输入你的网址后
and a search result would appear
搜索结果将会出现
that highlights your business.
并重点突出你的企业
In this example, the user typed
在这个例子中  用户输入了"apple"
"apple" and the search result
搜索结果显示了
shows the nearby Apple Union
附近的 Apple Union Square
Square location.
的位置
And you can see that the message
你可以看到
button is prominently featured.
Message 按钮被显著突出
Your user can start a
你的用户可以立即
conversation right from here
从这里开始对话
instead of hunting on the
而不是费劲地从网站
website for contact information.
寻找联系信息
Here is the Message button in
以下是 Message 按钮在
Search and in Siri and in Maps
Search Siri 和 Maps
too.
中的样子
The Message button can appear
Message 按钮可以出现在
for each one of your store
您任意一个
locations.
商店位置旁
We are also adding new support
我们还可以为无法显示地理位置的企业
for businesses that don't have
提供新的支持
locations, including those that
比如在线企业或者
might be online or app only.
只有 App 的企业
Now if you're an online
如果您是在线企业
business, or if there're no
或者附近
nearby locations, there will
没有相关地点
still be a search result
仍然会为您提供
available for you.
搜索结果
This is how search results might
如果附近没有 Apple 的商店
look in Safari if Apple had no
那么搜索结果在 Safari 中
nearby store locations.
将会这样呈现
Links are another great entry
链接是另一个你可以使用的
point that you can use to invite
很棒的入口来邀请
your customers into your
你的顾客到
Business Chat conversation.
Business Chat 对话中
You can put links on your
你可以将链接放在你的
websites, in your app, and in
网站  App
your emails.
和邮件中
When your customer taps your
当你的顾客点击链接时
link, it will open your Business
它会在支持设备
Chat conversation on supporting
上的 Messages 中打开
devices within the Messages app.
Business Chat 对话
To create your link, you'll need
要创建链接  你需要
your Business Chat ID, which you
Business Chat ID
will receive after you create
你会在创建账户后
your account.
收到此 ID
The next feature that I'd like
接下来
to review is something called
我想讲的功能叫
Chat Intent.
Chat Intent
Chat Intent is a great way to
Chat Intent 是为你的客户
provide better support to your
提供更好的支持方式
customers by helping you
通过
understand the context of their
帮助你理解
question.
他们问题的背景
When you create links, you can
当你创建链接时
tag them to identify where your
你可以给它们添加标签来说明
customer tapped or clicked it.
顾客可以轻点或点击的位置
There are two Chat Intent values
你可以使用
that you can use.
两种 Chat Intent 值
The first one is called intent
第一种叫 intent ID
ID and the second one is group
第二种叫 group ID
ID, and they're completely
他们是
optional.
完全可选的
They could be whatever you need
他们可以是
them to be.
你自定的
When your customer taps your
当顾客点击链接时
link and that link contains Chat
且链接包含 Chat Intent 值
Intent values, those values will
这些值
be passed back to you with the
会在下一条信息中
next message.
返还给你
Let's see how you might use
让我们看看
them.
你该如何使用它
Let's say your customer is
让我们假设你的客户
browsing one of your products
正在浏览你其中一个产品
and has a question about it.
并对此有疑问
You could use Chat Intent to
你可以使用 Chat Intent
know the product config so your
来了解产品配置
customer doesn't need to type it
这样你的客户就不需要
out.
将它打出来
For example, you could put the
例如你可以将
product details or the product
产品详情或产品编码
code into the Intent field so
放进 Intent 栏中
that your support agent can
这样你的支持人员就能
provide a faster answer to your
快速解答
customer.
客户的问题
Or maybe you have different
或者如果你有
internal teams that offer
不同的内部团队
specialized support, you could
提供专业支持
use Chat Intent to route
你可以使用 Chat Intent
messages to the relevant
把消息转给
internal team.
相关内部团队
In this case, you could put the
在这个例子中  你可以将
team code into the group field
团队编码放入 group 栏中
and that way you could route
这样你就可以
incoming messages to the team
把收到的信息
that handles that particular
转给专门处理
issue.
此类问题的团队
And sometimes your customers may
有时你的客户
want to chat with one of your
想要和某个特定地点
particular locations.
的商店交谈
In the future, you will be able
未来 你可以向 Apple Maps
to provide your locations and
提供位置信息
your location IDs to Apple Maps.
以及 location ID
Apple will automatically then
Apple 随后会自动
populate the Intent field with
在 Intent 栏中
your location ID.
填充你的 location ID
That way when the customer taps
这样当顾客
the message and sends their
点击 Message
message to that location, you
并向那个位置发送信息时
will know to which location they
你就会知道
were directing their message and
他们在向何处发送信息
then you will be able to route
然后你就可以
the message appropriately.
恰当地转发消息
So we just reviewed all the ways
所以我们刚刚回顾了
that your business might be
能让顾客找到你
found by your customer.
的所有方法
But once your customer taps that
一旦您的顾客点击了
Message button, they are then
Message 按钮
taken to your conversation
他们会被带至
inside of the Messages app.
Messages App 中与你对话
So let's explore some of the
所以让我们探索一下
features of those Business Chat
Business Chat 对话的
conversations.
一些功能
It's important to note that your
重要的一点是
customer must send the first
您的顾客必须
message to open the
发送首条消息
conversation.
来开始对话
But once that conversation is
一旦对话开始
open, you can then message back
你就可以回复消息
or send important notifications.
或发送重要通知
With your customer's message,
有了顾客的消息
you will also receive that
你还会收到
customer's opaque ID.
顾客的不透明 ID
This is a unique ID designed to
这是一个独特的 ID
preserve their anonymity until
用来保持他们的匿名性
they're ready to share more
直到他们准备和你分享
personal information with you.
更多个人信息
In addition, you will also
此外  你还会收到
receive the customer's language
顾客的母语种类
and device region so that you
以及设备所在区域以便你
can route their message to the
将他们的消息转给
internal team that's best
能更好解答
equipped to answer their
他们的问题
question.
的内部团队
As we saw in the video, the
如我们在视频中
conversation session is long
看到的那样
lived.
对话会长期保留
Your customer can return and
您的顾客可以
pick up where they left off at
随时回到
any time.
他们此前离开的地方
They should be able to just jump
他们可以直接进来
in and ask a quick question
快速问一个的问题
without having to re-identify
并不需要
themselves.
重新确认身份
And you can have their account
并且你可以提前得知
information ready so they can
他们的账户信息
get help without wasting time
这样在得到帮助时他们就不需要
describing what you should
浪费时间来说明你应该
already know.
提前了解的信息
After your customer sends the
在你的顾客发送首条消息后
first message, you might need
你可能需要
some personal details to assist
一些个人详细信息
them.
来帮助他们
So let's say you needed their
假设你需要
phone number.
他们的电话号码
You might ask and the QuickType
你问了之后
keyboard will make intelligent
QuickType 键盘会给出智能建议
suggestions so your customer can
这样你的顾客只需轻轻一点
reply with just a tap.
就能回复
The QuickType keyboard can make
QuickType 键盘可以
intelligent suggestions so your
给出智能建议
customers can easily provide
这样顾客可以轻易地提供
their email address, their phone
他们的邮箱地址
number, their postal address,
电话号码  邮寄地址
and even their location.
甚至他们的位置
Messages is a very personal
Messages 是一个
area.
非常私人的地方
This is where your customers
您的顾客在这里
communicate with their friends
和他们的朋友以及家人
and family.
进行交流
It's important to us that users
对我们来说重要的是
never receive unsolicited
用户永远不会收到
messages.
不请自来的消息
We wanted to give users full
我们想要给用户
control over their
与企业交流的
communications with businesses.
完全控制权
Users can manage their
用户可以通过
conversations by hiding alerts
隐藏提醒或
or by deleting the conversation.
删除对话来管理他们的对话
When they hide alerts, they will
当他们隐藏提醒时
continue to receive messages but
他们会继续接收消息
they won't be notified.
但不会收到通知
And if they delete the
如果他们删除了对话
conversation, that will block
这会屏蔽
all future messages from you.
所有你未来的消息
Next, attachments.
下面  附件
Because Business Chat is within
因为 Business Chat 存在于
the Messages app, Business Chat
Messages App 中
supports all of the standard
Business Chat 支持所有标准附件类型
attachment types like photos,
比如照片
videos, and documents.
视频和文档
For example, your customer might
例如您的顾客可以
send a photo of a product they
发送一张他们需要的产品的照片
might need, or your customer
或者您的顾客
might send a video of an area of
发送一段他们房屋区域的视频
their house to help you provide
来更好的
a more accurate quote and you
明确需求
can use attachments to send
您可以使用附件
forms or other important
来发送表格
information.
或其他重要信息
Next, let's cover some ways that
下面我们来说说一些
you can provide a better
可以让你为顾客带来更好体验
experience to your customers.
的方法
We wanted to create some
我们想创建一些
built-in features that help you
内置功能
provide a consistent engaging
帮助你在
experience for some common use
日常使用时
cases.
享受一贯的绝佳体验
It's important to note that
重要的是要注意
these features are built in, so
这些功能是内置的
they're available for you even
因此你即使没有自己的 App
if you don't have your own app.
他们还是可供你使用
The first is Time Picker.
第一个功能是 Time Picker
Scheduling appointments is a
预约时间是一种
common use case.
常见使用情况
You can use Time Picker to send
你可以使用 Time Picker 来发送
over a list of proposed times to
建议的时间列表
your customer to review.
以供顾客参考
Your customer can see if they
您的顾客可以看到
have a conflict with existing
这些时间是否与
appointments that they might
日历中已存在的事件
have in Calendar.
发生冲突
Your customer can review and
您的顾客可以参考
then choose the best option and
然后选择最佳选项
send their choice back to you.
并将选择结果发送给你
Choosing from a list of options
从选项列表中选择
is also another common use case.
也是一种常见使用情况
We created List Picker so you
我们创造了 List Picker
can provide a visual way to make
这样在选择时
a selection.
更加可视化
With List Picker, you can send
有了 List Picker
your customer a list of options.
你可以向顾客发送选项列表
Your customer can select one or
您的顾客可以选择一个或多个
more, depending on how you
这取决于你如何配置它
configured it, and then send a
然后将选择结果
choice back to you.
发送给你
Lastly, we know that payments is
最后我们知道支付
another common use case.
也是常见的使用情况
Apple Pay provides an easy and
Apple Pay 提供了便捷
secure way to pay.
又安全的支付方式
And if you're also a retailer
如果你是零售商
that wants a quick check-out
并且想要快速结账
process, customers can quickly
顾客可以迅速
and securely provide their
又安全地提供他们的
payment, shipping, and contact
支付 配送和联系信息
information and then check out
然后只需轻轻一点
with just one touch.
就能结账
The built-in features that we
我们刚才所讲到的
just covered offer a great
内置功能为一些
experience for some common use
常见情况提供了
cases.
绝佳体验
But we know that these just
但我们知道这些
scratch the surface of what's
只是所需功能的
needed.
皮毛
To customize the experience for
如果您想为您的企业定制体验
your business, you can extend
您可以通过使用
Business Chat by using the
去年发布的 iOS 10 中的
iMessage app framework released
iMessage App 框架
last year in iOS 10.
来扩展 Business Chat
With the Messages framework, you
有了 Messages 框架
can create app experiences that
你可以创造顾客能
your customers can use directly
直接从 Business Chat 中
within Business Chat.
使用的 App 体验
Essentially, you can pull in
重要的是
parts of your app into the
当你的顾客需要时
conversation just when your
你可以将您的 App 部分
customer needs it.
挪到对话中
Your app can appear like a
您的 App 可以像一个
message bubble.
信息气泡一样出现
For example, if the customer
例如如果顾客
needed to select their seats,
需要选座
they could get a bubble like
他们得到一个这样的气泡提示窗口
this, tap it, and then quickly
点击它那么就可以
complete the task.
快速完成任务
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
With iMessage apps, you can
有了 iMessage App
speed customers through common
你可以让顾客
issues and improve your support
更快解决常见问题并
team productivity.
提高你支持团队的效率
And Business Chat is a great way
并且 Business Chat
to introduce customers to your
是向顾客介绍你 App 的
app.
绝佳方式
If your customer doesn't yet
如果您的顾客还没有
have your app installed, they
安装您的 App
can tap to get the app right
他们在对话中点击
from within the conversation.
则可以直接获取 App
You can use your app to
你可以通过 Live Message layout
customize the look and behavior
使用您的 App
of Messages using Live Message
来定制 Messages 的样式
layouts.
和行为
You can customize the bubble,
您可以定制气泡提示窗口
for example, by adding a map or
比如添加地图
a live countdown, a simple form,
或实时倒计时  一个简单的表格
or any other interaction that
或其他通过你 App
you create using your app.
创建的互动
To learn more about how to
要了解更多关于
create iMessage apps, go to
创建 iMessage App 的信息  请访问
developer.apple.com/imessage.
developer.apple.com/imessage
Next, let's talk about getting
下面我们来讲讲
connected.
如何互联
As a business, you're going to
作为企业  你需要
need a customer service platform
一个支持 Business Chat
that supports Business Chat.
的客户服务平台
Your platform will help you
你的平台会帮你
connect, route messages
互联  分转内部消息
internally, and provide
以及
productivity tools for your
为你的团队提供
team.
效率工具
Your platform will also help
你的平台还会帮助
connect your apps into your
将你的 App 接入
support operations.
支持的活动
This is so that your team can
这样你的团队就能
send app experiences to your
让顾客体验到
customers.
App
As a business, you need to apply
作为企业  你需要在
for the developer preview at
register.apple.com
register.apple.com.
申请开发者预览版本
Likewise, if you are a customer
同理  如果你是一家支持
service platform that supports
Messaging 的客户服务平台
Messaging, you can also apply to
你也可以申请
offer Business Chat to your
并向你的客户提供
clients too.
Business Chat
So once your account is approved
一旦你的账户通过了
for Business Chat, you could
Business Chat 批准
receive messages from Apple
你就可以从 Apple 设备
devices.
接收消息
Let's say your customer sends a
假设你的顾客向你
message to you.
发送了一条消息
This message will first arrive
这条消息会首先到达
on Apple's Business Chat server.
Apple 的 Business Chat 服务器
From there, messages are passed
在那里  消息会传递给
to your customer service
你的客户服务平台
platform, and then your platform
随后你的平台
will route messages to the
将此消息分转给
appropriate person or team
企业内恰当的
within your business.
个人或团队
When they respond, your message
当他们作出回应时
is routed back to your customer.
消息发回给顾客
As I mentioned, during Business
我刚才提到了
Chat developer preview, your
在 Business Chat 开发者预览版本期间
business is not yet publicly
企业无法向公众
accessible.
提供服务
However, you can white list
但是你可以将员工
employees and these employees
列入白名单
can test the full experience,
这些员工可以测试全部功能
interact with your iMessage
与你的 iMessage App 互动
apps, and make sure that
并确保
everything is working properly.
一切都没有问题
OK, let's go through how to get
好 让我们回顾下
started.
如何入门
There are three things that you
你今天就可以做的
can do today.
有三件事
First, start developing.
一  开始开发
You can use the Business Chat
你可以使用 Business Chat Sandbox
Sandbox that Scotty will take us
Scottie 待会儿会
through next.
给我们介绍
Second, get connected on a
二  接入一个
customer service platform that
支持 Business Chat 的
supports Business Chat.
客户服务平台
And then, apply for early access
然后  申请 Business Chat 的
to Business Chat.
早期权限
With that, Scotty will take us
Scottie 会给我们带来
through a demo Business Chat
Business Chat Sandbox 演示
Sandbox and how you can use it
以及你如何使用它
to start developing and testing
来开始开发并
your use cases.
测试使用情况
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Alright, thanks, Grant.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢你 Grant
We're real excited about
我们为 Business Chat
Business Chat.
感到兴奋
We have developed an entire
我们开发出了一个完整的平台
platform that will allow
它允许每个人
everyone to communicate with
都能通过世界上
businesses directly through one
使用最多的 App - Messages
of the most used apps on the
来直接跟企业
planet, Messages.
进行交流
And, as you've seen, we've built
此外如你看到的
in some great software into
我们在每个 iOS 11 设备中
every iOS 11 device that makes
内置了一些很棒的软件
performing these common business
让完成这些常见任务
tasks simple and fun, including
变得简便有趣
making payments using Apple Pay,
包括使用 Apple Pay 进行支付
way better than trying to give
这比在手机上
your credit card information
给出你的信用卡信息
over the phone.
棒多了
And it's even way more secure.
并且它更加安全
Now, you can mix these built-in
现在你可以将这些内置功能
features with your own custom
和你创建的自己定制的
messages apps that you create
Messages App 融合
and we think there's some real
我们认为这对你来说
opportunity here for you to
是个很好的机会来
create some new really amazing
创造一些很棒的
customer engagement experiences.
客户参与新体验
Now we were so excited about all
现在我们对所有这些
of this, we wanted everyone to
感到兴奋  我们希望每个人
be able to try this out today
今天就能用你的 iOS 11 设备
using your iOS 11 device.
来尝试一下
As message app developers, you
作为 Message App 开发人员
can try integrating with your
你可以尝试与你的
messages apps.
Messages App 结合
As customer service platforms,
至于客户服务平台
you can see what formats we're
你可以看到通过网络
sending over the wire, or as a
我们发送的什么格式
business owner or someone who's
或作为企业老板
just interested, you can use the
或者只是感兴趣的人
Sandbox to dream up the next
你可以使用 Sandbox
great customer experience
来想象未来的绝佳
engagement.
客户参与体验
So what did we do?
所以我们做了什么
Well, as Grant showed, we have
嗯 Grant 刚刚展示了
this flow of information that
我们有这个传递的
goes through and what we've
信息流和我们已经创造的一些东西
created as the Sandbox is a way
Sandbox
-- Sandbox is pretty much like
就像
your own customer service
我们创造的属于你自己的
platform that we've created and
客户服务平台并且
we've put a web frontend on it.
我们为它做了网页前端
Now your business might have its
你的企业可能有自己
own web frontend but in this
网页前端 但在这里
case, this is a Sandbox
这是 Sandbox 环境
environment and you can use to
你可以用它来试验
play and we think it'll be great
我们觉得这样很棒
so you can experience these
所以你可以体验这些
features.
功能
So instead of talking about it,
我一直在说
let me give you a demo right
不如现在我来给大家
now.
演示一下
So I'm going to switch over to
我现在要切换到
the demo device here and I have
这里的演示设备
loaded up here the website for
我已经在左边加载了
Business Chat Sandbox on the
用于 Business Chat Sandbox 的网站
left and I have an iPhone here
我把 iPhone 界面放在这里的
on the right.
右边
And as Grant mentioned, the
Grant 刚才提到了
interactions with businesses
和企业之间的互动
have to be started by your iOS
必须由你的 iOS 设备
device.
来开始
Grant highlighted a lot of great
Grant 强调了很多很好的方式
ways that you can get to your
可以启动
Business Chat through things
Business Chat 比如
like Maps and Siri, but another
Maps 和 Siri 但还有个很好的
great way is QR codes.
方式就是二维码
And this has highlighted a new
而这就体现了
feature on iOS 11 where you can
iOS 11 的一个新功能
use your camera app to hover
你可以使用你的相机 App
over a QR code, which I'm going
悬停在二维码上
to do now, and you'll see up
我现在正在做
pops a message notification.
你可以看到弹出了一条消息通知
I can just tap this guy and I'm
我可以点击它
brought right into messages
然后我被转至 Messages
ready to start a communication
可以开始和
with Business Chat Sandbox.
Business Chat Sandbox 对话
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So keep in mind, this is the
所以请记住
setup process.
这是设置流程
I have logged in with my iCloud
我用 iCloud 账户
account to Business Chat Sandbox
登录了 Business Chat Sandbox
and I've scanned this QR code
然后我扫描了这个二维码
and I'm ready to start talking
然后我就可以
to a business.
和企业对话
I don't know any other platform
我不知道其他平台
that has it this easy.
有没有这么简便
So let's start sending a really
让我们先发送一条
profound message and say, "Hi."
意味深长的消息 “Hi”
And you'll see, boom, on the
你可以看到  咚  在左边
left, the Business Chat Sandbox
Business Chat Sandbox 更新了
updates since I've made
因为我已经和
communication with that
企业开始
business.
对话了
So what do we have here?
那么这里有什么呢
Well, along the top we have a
嗯  在上边我们有
bunch of tabs that highlight
一排标签
different functionality of
体现了 Business Chat
Business Chat.
的不同功能
We have Text so you can send
我们有 Text 这样你就可以
text back and forth.
来回发送文字
We have Attachment so you can
我们有 Attachment 这样你就可以
try sending files and other
发送文件
types of attachments back and
和其他类型的
forth.
附件
We have the Time Picker that
我们有 Time Picker
Grant highlighted.
Grant 刚才强调了
We have List Picker to be able
我们有 List Picker
to pick from a list.
可以从列表进行选择
We have everyone's favorite
我们有每个人的最爱
Apple Pay to collect payments
Apple Pay 来向顾客
from customers.
收款
We have My App, which allows you
我们有 My App 可以使你
to test integrating with your
测试整合后你自己的
own custom messages app.
定制 Messages App
And Raw JSON, which lets you try
以及 Raw JSON
out and modify the JSON and see
让你试用和修改 JSON
what happens when you customize
看看当你根据
this to your business
业务环境定制时
environment.
会发生什么
On the right, I have a
在右边
transcript showing the
文字记录展示了
communications between the
Sandbox 和我的设备
Sandbox and my device.
之间的对话
And at the bottom, we have a
在底部有一个
JSON tab, which actually shows
JSON 标签  向你展示了
you the formats that we're
我们在线上
sending over the wire.
发送的格式
This is really helpful when
当你在开发
you're developing customer
客户服务平台
service platforms or your own
或自己的 Messages App
messages apps to make sure
想确保没有问题时
you're getting things right.
会非常有用
So as a business, over here I
作为企业
might type a response to my
我想输入
profound "hi" and say something
来回复 “hi”
like, "How may I help you?"
比如说“请问有什么可以帮你”
And we can send that across and
我们可以发送过去
you'll see that sends and, boom,
你可以看到发送了 咚
we get that right here, great,
我们发到了右边的设备上
on the device.
太棒了
Great, so now we've established
所以现在我们已经
communication.
开始了沟通
Let's go to Attachments and see
让我们到 Attachments 看看
how we can use Attachments to
我们如何使用 Attachments
communicate with our customers.
来和顾客进行交流
I have an image here.
这里有张图片
We have some internals of what
我们有张 HomePod
the home pod might look like.
内部样子的图片
So yeah, let's send that to the
嗯  让我们把这个发给
customer.
顾客
OK, great, I got it on the
好 在右边
right.
看到了
That's what the inside of the
这就是
home pod looks like.
HomePod 里面的样子
Great. OK and we can even send
好  我们甚至还可以
images back.
发送照片过去
I can pull up the camera here
我可以在这里展开相机
and the camera comes up here, I
这里出现了相机界面
can take a lovely photo of all
我可以拍一张所有
you in the audience.
观众的照片
Very good.
很好
And I can send this now back to
我可以将这张照片
the business and tell the
发给企业并告诉他
business, great.
好
Just give it a second to
给它一点时间
receive.
来接收
And here it is.
有了
Great. Now I've told the
很好  我已经告诉了
business all the people looking
企业以后想要
to communicate with them in the
跟他们交流
future.
的所有人
That's great [applause].
非常棒 [掌声]
So let's create a scenario that
所以让我们创建一个
you might want to go through as
作为企业你可能
a business to try out Business
会经历的场景来尝试一下
Chat.
Business Chat
Let's go on my iOS device and we
让我们回到我的 iOS 设备
want to highlight probably
我们想重点讲下
something that people experience
人们会可能会经常遇到的
pretty often.
一些事情
Let's message this business and
让我们给这个企业发消息
say something like, "Let's check
让我们说
the status of my orders."
检查一下我的订单状态
Now this could be any business,
这可以是任何企业
shipping any kind of order, so
发出任何形式的订单
we're going to send this to the
我们现在把这个发送给企业
business and alright.
好了
So now we're going to use the
现在我们要使用
List Picker to send a list of
List Picker 来发送
items of the orders that the
企业所知道的
business knows about to this
此顾客的
customer.
订单列表
Now as Grant mentioned, we have
Grant 刚才提到了
long-lived IDs.
我们有长期保留的 ID
So previously I had already
之前我已经认证了
authenticated myself, so the
自己的身份
business knows who I am.
所以企业知道我是谁
So they can internally pull up
所以在内部他们可以
all of the orders that have been
找出这个顾客的
assigned to that customer.
所有相关订单
So I'm going to -- I have some
我在这里保存了
saved JSON example here that I'm
一些 JSON 例子
going to drag in and you'll see
我把它拖进来
I filled out the form here.
你可以看到我填好了这张表
So what do we have?
有什么呢
At the top we have the received
在顶部我们有
message.
Received Message
This is the message that gets
这是企业要发送的
sent by the business and then
消息然后
received onto the customer's
顾客的设备
device.
会接收
You can see you can specify an
你看你可以指定
icon.
图标
There's a title and subtitle of
聊天气泡有标题和副标题
the bubble and we have different
并且我们有不同的
size formats.
尺寸格式
You can actually modify these to
你可以根据你喜欢的风格
whatever style you'd like.
来修改这些
Down below, we specify the
在下面我们
items.
注明商品
So here we have -- You can see I
这里你可以看到
have some items here that I have
我有一些即将收到的
incoming.
商品
I have some T-shirts delivering
我有一些今天发出的
today.
T 恤
I have a new iPad Pro coming on
我有个六月 12 号配送的
June 12th and some Yerba Mate
iPad Pro 和一些 Yerba Mate
coming, delicious.
真棒
We can specify if we want to
我们可以说明如果我们想
select multiple items.
选择多项商品
So this allows the customer to
这可以让顾客
pick from multiple instead of
从多个中选择
one at a time.
而不是一次一个
For this case, let's talk about
在这个例子里  让我们先
just one shipment at the start.
只谈一次配送
And you see I can go ahead and
你看我可以继续
add or remove other items and
添加或删除其他商品
add or remove other sections as
以及添加或删除其他
well.
部分
But we're just going to start
但在这里我们将
with this one section for this
只从一个部分
case.
开始
Down below I have the Reply
在下面是
Message.
Reply Message
Reply Message is the look of the
Reply Message 是当我把
bubble when I send back the
选择结果发回
choice that I've made back to
给企业时的
the business.
气泡样式
Here, just like the received
这里就像 Received Message
message, I have title and
有标题和副标题
subtitle and I can specify the
并且我可以指定
icon style.
图标样式
On the right, now, you can see
在右边现在你可以看到
the JSON has been updated to
JSON 已经更新了
include all of the things I've
包括了我在表格中
specified in the form.
指定的所有东西
We have a section for images
我们有一块图片区域
where we have base64 encoded
图片是 base64 编码的
images with an identifier.
且包含标识符
Below that we have the List
在下面是 List Picker 区域
Picker section where you specify
你可以在这里指定
the sections and the items that
区域以及我在左边
I've typed on the left, things
输入的商品比如
like the T-shirts, title, an
T 恤的标题
image identifier which
对应于上面
references the base64 encoded
base64 编码图片的图片标识符
image above, and my other items
以及我的其他商品
and some other fields,
和其他栏
specifying order, subtitle, et
指定顺序 副标题
cetera.
等等
Down below, you see we have the
在下面 你看到有
received message and reply
receivedMessage 和 replyMessage 区域
message mirroring what I've
反映了我在左边
entered on the left, which
输入的内容
specify how the bubbles will
这些内容具体说明了
look when I send them to my
当发送至设备时气泡框的
device.
样式
Alright, let's give this
好了 我们
customer a way to select from
让顾客从这些选项中
these.
进行选择
I'm going to send this to the
我把这个发到设备上
device and you see on the right
你可以看到在右边
of my iPhone up comes bubble for
我的 iPhone 上出现了一个气泡框
me to select the package.
以供我选择包裹
When I tap this bubble, up come
当我点击气泡框时
the choices that I specified on
出现了我在左边指定的
the left.
选项
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Great. So, let's take a look at
好了 让我们看看
these.
这些
So I'm really inquiring about
所以我现在要查询
this iPad that I'm getting on
我即将在周一收到的
Monday.
iPad
So I'm going to select this and
我选择它然后
you see I tap that and up comes
你看到我点击时
the response that I'm ready to
出现了我准备好
send back to the business.
发送回企业的回复
I can go ahead and just send
我可以继续并
that back.
发送回去
And now in the Business Chat
现在 Business Chat Sandbox 中
Sandbox, in the transcript
的消息记录里
you'll see that the List Picker
你可以看到 List Picker
response has been highlighted so
的回复已经强调显示了
the business knows which item
这样企业就知道
I'm actually interested in.
我感兴趣的是哪个商品
Alright, great.
好
So, let's continue the
让我们继续
experience here.
这个体验
Let's go from the business and
让我们在企业这边说
say, "What would you like help
关于这个 iPad
with for this iPad?"
有什么需要帮忙的
So what I really want to do is
我想做的是
this iPad is scheduled for
这个 iPad 将会
delivery on Monday but I don't
在周一送达
really want to wait around for
但我不想等这么久
this to come.
才收到
I want to go and pick this up as
我想自己取走
soon as possible, as this is one
越快越好因为
of those new iPads.
这是一台新推出的 iPad
So I'm going to say, "Let's
所以我说
schedule a pickup."
让我们安排一次取件
So we're assuming now this
我们现在假设
business actually has some sort
这个企业有
of pickup location and to do
取件点
that we're going schedule a
要取件我们要预约
time.
时间
So we're going to switch to the
所以我们将转到
Time Picker so we can schedule a
Time Picker 这样我们就可以
time for me to go and pick up
安排一个时间让我去取
that iPad.
那个 iPad
I have some JSON saved down
我为这个保存了一些 JSON
below for that.
在这下面
So I'm going to drag that in
我现在把它拖到这栏
[inaudible] and we'll try that
让我们再
again.
试一次
OK. So here, we have specified
好现在我们为已收到的消息
some different images and
指定了一些
different icon styles for
不同的图片和不同的
received message.
图标样式
This is just like a List Picker.
这跟 List Picker 一样
It has a received message.
它也有 Received Message.
This is the bubble that comes in
这是出现在顾客
to the customer's device.
设备上的气泡框
I've set a title for "Hold iPad
我已经设置了标题为
for pickup" and a subtle
" Hold iPad for pickup"和副标题
"Schedule a time."
"Schedule a time"
I also have some details about
同时关于这个预约
this appointment or schedule.
还有一些细节
I have a name and optionally you
有预约名称另外你还可以
can include location details.
选择额外添加位置信息
So in this -- A lot of times,
在这里 -- 有很多时间
you know, appointments include
你知道  预约包括
an actual location that you're
你可以去的
going to.
实际地点
And for that, we can let you
对此  我们让你可以
specify a name, a lat, long, and
指定名称  经纬度
then the user can actually route
然后用户就可以
to that on their device, which
在他们设备上规划路线
I'll show you, momentarily.
稍后我会演示
Then we can specify time slots,
然后我们可以指定时间段
pick from a calendar, the time
从日历中选择
of day, and the duration of that
当天时间以及预约的
appointment.
持续时长
Down below, I have the reply
在下面是 Reply Message
message which is used of course
当然是用来
to show what happens when you
展示当你向企业
send back the message to the
发回消息后
business.
会发生什么
Now on the right, you can see
现在在右边你可以看到
the JSON has been updated to
JSON 已经更新了
also include our common images
包括了常见的图片格式
format but below we have the
但在下面有
event details and this specifies
事件详细信息
things like your time slots.
这个指定了比如你的时间段
These are all GMT dates and
这些都是 GMT 日期和时间格式
times with their duration in
持续时间
seconds.
以秒表示
Below that, I have location
在这下面
information specified with the
位置信息指定了
title, lat, long, and our
标题  经度  纬度
familiar received and reply
以及我们熟悉的已收到
message.
和回复消息
So let's schedule this
所以让我们
appointment.
预约一下
Time is marching on.
时间在流逝
Let's send that over to the
让我们把这个发送到设备
device and you see now on the
现在你看到在
iPhone here, I have a "Hold iPad
这里的 iPhone 上出现了
for pickup."
"Hold iPad for pickup."
I can go ahead and tap this.
我可以点击它
And you see we're displaying the
你看现在展示的是
options that the user can choose
顾客可以选择的我刚刚
that I've selected.
选出来的选项
I can show more or show less but
我可以展开或收起
we by default show the top
但默认情况下只显示
three.
前三个
I also -- We're tying in to iOS'
我们在将
built-in functionality of
iOS 的内置功能 EventKit
EventKit, so you can see if
整合进去这样你就可以看到
there's any conflicts on your
是否和你日历中的事件发生冲突
calendar to help you better
帮你更好地
schedule the time.
安排时间
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Now I do have an appointment at
现在我确实在 11:00 有一个预约
11:00 but this iPad is way more
但这个 iPad 比那个
important than that.
重要的多
So I'm going to take an early
所以我打算早点吃午饭
lunch and schedule for 11 a.m.
并预约在上午 11 点
I'd like to go and pick up this
我要去拿
iPad.
这个 iPad
So you see now I have the time
你看我已经选择好了
selected.
时间
I can go ahead and send this
我可以继续把这个
back to the Business Chat
发回给 Business Chat Sandbox
Sandbox and in the transcript,
在消息记录里
in the Sandbox, on the right, we
在 Sandbox 里  右边
have the time that I've selected
出现了我选择的
notified to the business.
通知企业的时间
Now, I did mention that we have
我刚才提到了我们有
this location detail.
这个位置详细信息
So on the iPhone, once I've sent
所以在 iPhone 上
this back to the business, I can
当我把这个发回企业
actually go ahead and tap that
我可以继续点击那个气泡框
bubble and I get the information
然后我收到了我发回
that I've sent back, including
的信息包括
the time and location.
时间和地点
From here, I can easily add this
在这里  我可以轻易地将
appointment right to my calendar
这个预约添加到我的日历中
or get directions right in Maps
或直接从 Maps
to the location that I've
获取到我指定的地点
specified.
的路线
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
OK, we're going to close that.
好了我们把这个关掉
Great. So these are highlighting
所以这些体现了
some of the built-in
你在和 Business Chat
interactions that you may
互动时可能
encounter when you're
会碰到的
interfacing with Business Chat,
一些内置互动
but we also wanted to highlight
但我们还想说
that you can integrate this with
你可以将此与
your own messages apps and take
你自己的 Messages Apps 整合
more advantage of the native
并善加利用
power of iOS.
iOS 的原生功能
So let's switch over to the My
让我们切换到
App tab.
My App 窗口
And let's talk about this.
让我们讲讲这个
From here, we have a bunch of
在这里有很多字段
fields that you can use to
你可以用来和
communicate with your message
你的 Message App
app.
进行沟通
The top two fields allow you to
前面两栏让你可以
link to the app, allow your
链接到 App
customer to link to the app in
允许你的顾客链接到 App
case they don't have it
以防他们还
installed.
未安装
You pull out your iTunes URL ID
你调出你的 iTunes URL ID
and enter that here and you
在这里输入
provide your app name, which is
然后提供你的 App 名称
shown in the transcript.
名称显示在消息记录中
Then we have the URL field.
然后是 URL 字段
So in messages apps, one of the
所以在 Messages App 中
preferred ways to communicate
和你的 Messages App
between your messages apps is
交流的首选方式实际上
actually via URL.
是通过 URL
And you can put URL keys and
你可以将 URL key 以及
values here that the app can
value 放在这里这样 App 就可以
then read.
读取
Down below we have the team
在下面我们有
identifier and bundle
Team Identifier 和
identifier.
Bundle Identifier.
These are used so iOS actually
用了它们 iOS 就
knows which message extension to
知道该实例化哪个
instantiate.
信息后缀
And we have an optional session
另外我们还有个可选的 Session Identifier
identifier used in case you have
以防你同时有
multiple message app
多个 Message App
transactions going at once, you
交易进行
can then identify, which one
你就可以识别
you're actually talking about.
你实际要用的是哪个
Live Message Layouts, as Grant
Live Message Layout
mentioned, is a new feature in
Grant 刚才提到了
iOS 11 that lets your message
是 iOS 11 里的一个新功能
bubbles draw all the content,
让你的消息气泡框生成所有内容
providing way more
提供了更多
functionality, native
的功能
functionality from iOS, right in
iOS 的原生功能
the messages transcript.
就在消息记录里
However, if you're sending these
但是如果你将这些
to older iOS devices, they might
发送到老版本的 iOS 设备上
not support Live Message Layout
它们可能不支持 Live Message Layout
as well as other platforms such
以及其他平台比如
as the Mac or the Watch.
Mac 或 Watch
For that, we allow you to enter
对此我们允许你
the information that you may
针对发送不成功的气泡框
have for the fallback bubble so
输入信息
at least they can see that
这样他们至少可以看到
something was received on those
在那些设备上接收到了
devices.
一些信息
So I'm going to go ahead and
我将继续
drag in some content I have for
拖进一些我为 App 准备的
the app here.
内容
And OK, so now you see these
好了  现在你可以看到
fields are filled out and I have
这些字段已经填充好并且
specified some URL parameters,
我已经指定了 URL 参数
which are then read by the
参数稍后会被设备上的
built-in message app on the
内置 Message App
device.
读取
So I have preinstalled already
我已经在这个 iPhone 上
on this iPhone a message app so
提前安装了一个 Message App
I don't have to go and show you
这样我就不需要向你们展示
how that can download from the
如何从 App Store
app store.
进行下载
On the right, you can also see
在右边你可以看到
the JSON contents is now updated
JSON 内容已经更新了
with the fields like you've seen
包括你在上面看到的字段
above, app ID, app name, URL,
App ID  App 名称 URL
some other information including
以及一些其他信息包括
the received message fallback
Received Message
information.
发送成功信息
So I'm going to go ahead and
所以我将继续
send this but before I do,
发送这个  但在这之前
remember I've established
请记住我已经
communication with this business
和这个企业建立了
already.
对话
So time may have passed and what
一段时间过去了
this bubble is going to
这个气泡框想强调的是
highlight is I actually have a
我有一个包裹
shipment that's scheduled for
预定将在
delivery today.
今天送达
So I'm going to send that now
我现在要发送这个
and you'll see that I have these
你将看到我这些
T-shirts scheduled for delivery
T 恤预定在今天 WWDC 期间
today at WWDC.
送达
Now there's supposed to be --
现在这里应该有 --
There's the map there.
这里有个地图
Hold up. I tapped the wrong guy
等等我点错了
there.
这里  向我展示了一张
a map.
地图
Showing me a map of where those
展示了一张预定送货
are scheduled for delivery.
地点的地图
So this is [applause] -- This is
所以这就是 [掌声]  这是
a -- This is just a notification
应该  这只是一个通知
that may have come in randomly
可能会随机出现
as you have this Business Chat
当你设置好 Business Chat
environment set up.
环境后
But -- And actually, this is
但是  实际上
also using Live Message Layout.
这同样使用了 Live Message Layout
So you can see I have a map here
你可以看到这里有张地图
and the bubble format has this
这个气泡样式
green footer.
有绿色脚注
It doesn't look anything like
这可能跟你在 iOS 10 中
the bubbles that you may have
见到的气泡框
seen in iOS 10.
完全不同
That's because this is all
这是因为它从原生系统
drawing the content natively.
自动生成内容
So what you can see is I have
你可以看到
these T-shirts scheduled for
我为 WWDC 预定了这批 T 恤
WWDC and they're scheduled for
并且它们预计
delivery today but it looks like
今天送货 但是似乎
on the map that they're
在地图上
scheduled for somewhere in San
预计送货到
Francisco.
San Francisco
So that's not right.
这明显不对
Let's tap this bubble and bring
让我们点击这个气泡框
up our message app.
打开我们的 Message App
And now you can see that I have
现在你可以看到
incorrectly scheduled these
我错误地安排了
T-shirts for Moscone.
这批 T 恤送到 Moscone
But now we're down in San Jose.
但我们现在在 San Jose
So we're going to have to do
所以我们必须做些什么
something about that, but before
但在这之前
we do, you can see that this is
你可以看到
actually this is a live map that
在 Messages 里这实际上
I have here inside Messages.
是一张实时地图
Everything you can do with
你在 Messages App 里
Messages apps, you can do here
能做的所有事都可以
in the Business Chat and this --
在 Business Chat 里完成
And we also have our current
这里有我们
location here in San Jose.
在 San Jose 的当前位置
So you're able to tie in to all
所以你可以整合
of the great powerful features
iOS 中所有很棒的功能
of iOS, right in your business
到你的 Business Chat 中
This is not a web page.
这不是一个网页
So now we'd like to reroute
现在我们想重新
these to here because this is
安排到这里因为这是
the last day of the show and we
展会的最后一天
really got to get these T-shirts
我们真的需要在这里拿到
here.
T 恤
So I'm going to tap my current
所以我点击我的当前位置
location and let's specify that
让我们说明
we want the shipment rerouted to
我们想将送货目的的改到
my current location.
我的当前位置
There's a $15 charge but I'll
有 15 美元费用但我
have to expense that.
也必须花费
We're going to go ahead and
我们继续
confirm that we want this
确认我们想
rerouted to San Jose Convention
重新改到 San Jose Convention Center
Center and I'm going to go ahead
然后
and send that back to the
将这个发回
business.
企业
And you'll see in the Business
你可以看到在 Business Chat Sandbox
Chat Sandbox, now we've received
中我们现在收到了 URL
the URL, which specifies the new
其中指定了我们
location that we've designated
期望送达的
for the shipment.
新地址
Great. So that's showing
太棒了  刚才展现的
integration with your messages
是Messages App
apps.
的整合
But there's one more thing and
但还有件事
that we've scheduled a reroute
我们安排了一次重新派送
and that's going to cost us $15.
这将花费我们 15 美元
So for that we're going to
对此我们
request a payment from our
要让顾客
customers using Apple Pay.
使用 Apple Pay 进行支付
Now I'm going to drag in our
现在我要把
Apple Pay JSON here and you see
Apple Pay JSON 拖到这里
we have our familiar received
你看在上面有我们熟悉的
message at the top specifying an
Received Message 指定了
image and title and subtitle of
图像以及气泡框的标题
this bubble.
和副标题
And down below, we can specify
在下面我们可以定义
our items.
我们的商品
Here, we have a same-day
这里  有当天
shipment reroute that going to
重新配送  这将
cost you 15 bucks and we have a
花费你 15 美元
total price as well.
此外还有总价
Optionally now, we can also
现在我们还可以选择
specify shipping methods.
指定配送方式
For this, this actually is the
对此  这个实际上属于
reroute.
重新配送
So I'm not going to specify
所以我不会指定
shipping methods.
配送方式
We also have fields that you may
如果你以前
be familiar with if you've done
做过 Apple Pay 开发
Apple Pay development in the
你可能会很熟悉
past.
这些字段
We have -- If you'd like to
我们有  如果你想指定
specify the Apple Pay sheet
Apple Pay 表单
should require your billing
会需要你的账单地址
address or your shipping address
或收货地址
and what merchant capabilities
以及你的平台
your platform may contain.
包含的商户支持
Now these are all standard Apple
这些都是标准的
Pay functions.
Apple Pay 功能
We didn't do anything custom
我们在此处没有进行任何
here.
自定义
So if you're familiar developing
如果你很熟悉
with Apple Pay, this is, these
Apple Pay 开发
are things that you've already
这些是你已经
implemented.
实施过的
We also followed a very common
我们还遵照了一种非常常见的
Apple Pay JS format for the
针对 JSON 的 Apple Pay
JSON, which I'll show you over
JS 格式  我待会儿会在这里向你们
here.
展示
So for the JSON for this
关于这个请求的 JSON
request, we have our received
我们有 receivedMessage
message and we have our images,
我们有 images
as you've seen before, but now
就像你之前看到的
we have a payment object which
但现在我们有一个支付对象
contains a payment request.
包含了 paymentRequest
This contains line items, same
这包括了 lineItems
day shipment reroute for 15
same day shipment reroute
bucks, and a total.
花 15 美元以及一个总价
And then we also have our Apple
然后我们还有
Pay section, which contains
Apple Pay 区域包括了
information for what networks we
如下信息
support, merchant capabilities,
我们支持的网络 merchantCapabilities
and what types of currency we
以及我们支持的
support.
货币类型
Now at the bottom, here, you'll
现在这里的下面
also see we have some other URLs
你还看得我们有一些其他的 URL
and this is kind of interesting.
这非常有趣
So what we've done is we've
我们提供了
provided a bunch of URLs that
一些当你将
you can use when you integrate
Apple Pay 和你的业务整合时
Apple Pay with your business.
可以使用的 URL
The first one, payment Gateway
第一个 paymentGatewayUrl
URL, allows your business to
允许你的企业
send its encrypted payload to
发送加密的有效传输负载
actually process the payment.
来处理支付
Great. We also have three URLs
好了  我们还有另外三个 URL
that are used when the Apple Pay
他们被用于当 Apple Pay
sheet is up on the screen.
表单出现在屏幕上时
If you change your payment
如果你将你的支付方式
method from let's say a debit
从比如借记卡
card to a credit card, we're
变成信用卡
going to hit this URL so you may
我们将点击这个 URL 这样你会
want to in some cases maybe
在某些情况下可能
change what offerings you have.
改变了你拥有的优惠条件
Some businesses may offer
一些企业可能
discounts for certain types of
会针对特定类型的银行卡
cards.
提供折扣
When you change your shipping
当你更改你的运输方式时
method, we also have a chance to
我们也有机会
hit a server and update your
上传服务器并更新你的
shipment items.
运输商品
So let's say we are switching
假设我们将从
from ground to overnight
陆运变为隔夜送达
delivery, we might have to
我们可能需要
update your line items and your
更新你的条目以及
total.
总价
And then your shipping contact,
然后你的派送联系人
if suddenly I want this package
如果我突然想把这个包裹
delivered to Hawaii, you might
送到夏威夷
want to update all your shipping
你需要更新所有
methods, line items, and totals.
运输方式 条目以及总价
We then have a fallback URL,
我们还有个 fallbackUrl
which is used in case the
以防顾客
customer doesn't have Apple Pay
的设备上
on their device.
没有 Apple Pay
You can then specify a URL that
你还可以指定一个 URL
when tapping the Apple Pay
当点击 Apple Pay 气泡框时
bubble will take you to a web
会转到你选择的
page of your choice.
网页上
And then finally, an order
最后是一个
tracking URL.
orderTrackingUrl
This is used once the payment is
一旦支付
complete.
完成
So we've already sent the
我们已经通过
payment through the payment
paymentGatewayUrl
gateway URL but your business
发送了支付  但你的企业
may have a separate system that
可能会有一个单独的系统来
handles all your orders and
处理所有订单而
that's what this URL is used
这就是这个 URL
for.
的用处
Great. OK, let's send this to
好  让我们把这个
the device so we can collect
发到设备上这样我们可以
this $15 and gets these
得到 15 美元
T-shirts.
收到 T 恤
So you see on the device now up
你看在设备上出现了
comes our shipment reroute Apple
重新运输的
Pay Button.
Apple Pay 按钮
And I can go ahead and just tap
我可以继续点击
this bubble and up pops the
这个气泡框然后弹出了
familiar Apple Pay sheet.
熟悉的 Apple Pay 表单
From here, all I have to do is
在这里我只需要
touch ID.
Touch ID
The payment gets processed, sent
交易进行处理
back to the business, and the
发回给企业
bubble is updated with paid, and
然后气泡框更新为已支付
that's it.
就这样
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Alright, so let's go back to
好了让我们回到之前的
some slides.
幻灯片
Business Chat Sandbox is
Business Chat Sandbox
available at this URL.
可在这个 URL 获取
We think this is really cool and
我们觉得这非常棒
it's a way where you can just
你可以直接进来
jump in, get started with
今天就用你的
Business Chat today with your
iOS 11 设备
iOS 11 device.
使用 Business Chat 吧
We're really excited to see what
我们非常期待看到
kind of great experiences you
你们能借此创造出怎样的
can create.
绝佳体验
And with something like Business
有了 Business Chat Sandbox
Chat Sandbox, you really have a
你就有了一块画板
sketchpad to create the next
来创造下一个
great business customer
优秀的企业顾客
experience.
体验
Thank you.
谢谢！
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Scotty.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢你 Scottie
That was great.
非常棒
Alright, step two, get
好了  第二步
connected.
去连接
You need to work with a customer
你需要和一个支持
service platform that supports
Business Chat 的客户服务平台
Business Chat and we've already
协作并且我们已经
integrated with LivePerson,
整合了 LivePerson
Nuance, Genesys, and Salesforce.
Nuance  Genesys 和 Salesforce
These companies can help you get
这些公司可以帮助你
your business ready for Business
让你的企业准备好
Chat.
Business Chat
These companies will help you
这些公司会帮你
connect, route your messages,
连接  分转消息
and integrate your iMessage
以及整合你的
apps.
iMessage App
They'll also add intelligent
他们还会添加一些智能工具
tools to enhance your agent
来提升你职员的效率
productivity and help you manage
并帮你在各个
your communications across your
平台间管理
various channels.
进行通讯交流
Next, step three.
下一个  第三步
You can apply now for early
你现在可以申请
access to Business Chat by going
Business Chat 的早期权限
to register.apple.com.
通过访问 register.apple.com
And as a final note, when
最后提醒一下
designing your solution, please
在设计你的解决方案时
keep in mind that your customers
请牢记您的顾客
today understand the Call
完全理解电话
button.
按钮的功能
They know the type of support
他们知道当他们使用电话时
that they will receive from you
能从你那里得到
when they use the telephone.
怎样的帮助
Now, when they see your new
现在当他们看到了新的
Message button, they should know
Message 按钮时  他们应该知道
that they'll receive the
有了 Business Chat
equivalent or better support
他们会得到
with Business Chat.
更好的帮助
Help us make Business Chat an
让我们一起
awesome user experience right
马上赋予 Business Chat
out of the gate.
优秀的客户体验吧
So to recap, we went through the
总结一下我们讲了
various entry points.
很多入门点
You can use them to help
你可以用他们来帮助
customers find your business.
顾客找到你的企业
We also reviewed the built-in
我们还梳理了内置功能
features, the iMessage apps that
你可以使用
you can use to create a great
iMessage App 来创造
customer experience.
绝佳用户体验
So start today at
今天从
developer.apple.com/
developer.apple.com/
businesschat.
businesschat 开始
For more information about the
更多关于会议的信息
session, you can also go here.
你可以访问这里
Thanks, everyone.
谢谢大家